

# Varun R Gupta

Programmer, Web Developer & Designer

52, 11th Main, 30th Cross Banashankari 2nd Stage Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

- **&** +91 97398 56528
- 🙏 varungupta3009

# Experience

**Corporate Operations Engineer** 



Google

Jan 2022 – Present (4 mos)

IT Resident

Aug 2021 - Jan 2022 (6 mos)

**Data and Reporting Analyst Hewlett Packard Enterprise** 

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 (7 mos)



Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University

Jan 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 yr 9 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

# Education



**PES University** 

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

K-PUC (CS), Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi 2015 - 2017



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 - 2015

# **Publications & Awards**

Twitter Spam Review Detection Using Hybrid Machine Learning Techniques Springer, November 2021, ISBN: 978-981-16-3690-5

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

# Languages

हिंदी (Hindi) ಕನ್ನಡ (Kannada) English

## **Hobbies**

Reading

Gaming

Virtual Aviation

Music

# Knowledge and Skills

Pyth	ıon	3
------	-----	---

Experience

Skill

## **JavaScript**

Experience

Skill

#### C/C++

Experience

Skill

## Windows 7/8/10

Experience

Skill

#### Frontend Design and Development

Experience •

#### **Full-Stack Web Development**

Experience

Skill

### Angular (TS), React (JS/TS)

Experience •

Skill

## WordPress, CMS

Experience

Skill

#### Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

Experience •

#### Adobe After Effects and Premiere Pro

Experience •

# Blender, Pixar Renderman

Experience

Skill

## Cloud Architechture (GCP)

Experience

Skill

## About me

I am an experienced developer with proficiency in web design. Fluent in many computing languages with over 11 years of experience in Python, C++, and JS. Polymath, geek, and love to explore the bleeding edge of technology and internet. I am also a hobbyist designer and hacker.

# Let's Connect

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile to stay regularly updated, and to get in touch with me instantly.

